<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-11-29T14:09:33+02:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">my-project-jekyll</title><subtitle>From beginner to professional chef.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Duck with spiced red wine sauce and braised cabbage</title><link href="/2018/11/27/duck.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Duck with spiced red wine sauce and braised cabbage" /><published>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/27/duck</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/27/duck.html">&lt;div class=&quot;ingredients-wrapper&quot;&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;4 pontiac potatoes, peeled, cut into 2cm cubes&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 bunch thyme sprigs&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;4 garlic cloves&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;4 x 240g duck legs*&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 red onion, halved, sliced&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 red cabbage (750g), finely shredded&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;8 dried juniper berries*&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;3 cups (750ml) dry red wine&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;250g jar spiced redcurrant jelly*&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Chopped flat-leaf parsley, to garnish&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;method&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 class=&quot;header-method&quot;&gt;Method&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 1&lt;/span&gt;Preheat the oven to 200°C. Place the potato in a large saucepan of cold salted water.
            Bring to the boil and cook for 2 minutes. Drain, rinse under cold water and dry well with paper towel. Toss
            in 1 tablespoon of the oil. Lay thyme and garlic in a roasting pan, place duck on top and scatter potatoes
            around. Season and roast for 45 minutes, turning potatoes occasionally, until duck is cooked and potatoes
            are golden.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 2&lt;/span&gt;Meanwhile, heat remaining tablespoon of oil in a large pan over medium heat. Cook onion
            for 3-4 minutes. Add cabbage, sugar, juniper berries and 350ml wine, then bring to the boil. Cover and
            simmer over low heat, stirring occasionally, for 35 minutes. Stir in 2 tablespoons of jelly. Place the
            remaining jelly and wine in a pan and simmer over medium heat for 4-5 minutes until reduced and syrupy.
            Divide the cabbage among plates top with the duck, then drizzle with the sauce. Serve with potatoes.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">4 pontiac potatoes, peeled, cut into 2cm cubes 2 tablespoons olive oil 1 bunch thyme sprigs 4 garlic cloves 4 x 240g duck legs* 1 red onion, halved, sliced 1/2 red cabbage (750g), finely shredded 2 tablespoons brown sugar 8 dried juniper berries* 3 cups (750ml) dry red wine 250g jar spiced redcurrant jelly* Chopped flat-leaf parsley, to garnish Method Step 1Preheat the oven to 200°C. Place the potato in a large saucepan of cold salted water. Bring to the boil and cook for 2 minutes. Drain, rinse under cold water and dry well with paper towel. Toss in 1 tablespoon of the oil. Lay thyme and garlic in a roasting pan, place duck on top and scatter potatoes around. Season and roast for 45 minutes, turning potatoes occasionally, until duck is cooked and potatoes are golden. Step 2Meanwhile, heat remaining tablespoon of oil in a large pan over medium heat. Cook onion for 3-4 minutes. Add cabbage, sugar, juniper berries and 350ml wine, then bring to the boil. Cover and simmer over low heat, stirring occasionally, for 35 minutes. Stir in 2 tablespoons of jelly. Place the remaining jelly and wine in a pan and simmer over medium heat for 4-5 minutes until reduced and syrupy. Divide the cabbage among plates top with the duck, then drizzle with the sauce. Serve with potatoes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Beef with freekeh and cranberry salad</title><link href="/2018/11/27/beef.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beef with freekeh and cranberry salad" /><published>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/27/beef</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/27/beef.html">&lt;div class=&quot;ingredients-wrapper&quot;&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/4 cup massaman curry paste&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2cm piece fresh ginger, finely grated&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 garlic cloves, crushed&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 lemongrass stalk, white part only, very finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;600g beef rump steak, trimmed&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons sweet chilli sauce&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons white vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;3 baby cucumbers, thinly sliced into rounds&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;400g chat potatoes&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon peanut oil&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons tamarind puree&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;method&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 class=&quot;header-method&quot;&gt;Method&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 1&lt;/span&gt;Combine 2 tablespoons curry paste with 1 tablespoon water, ginger, garlic and lemongrass.
            Place beef in a shallow glass or ceramic dish. Rub all over with paste mixture. Cover. Refrigerate for 3
            hours or overnight.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 2&lt;/span&gt;Place potatoes in a large saucepan. Cover with cold water. Bring to the boil over high
            heat. Reduce heat to medium. Boil for 10 to 12 minutes or until just tender. Drain. Cool for 15 minutes.
            Slice thickly. Drizzle with peanut oil. Season with salt and pepper.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 3&lt;/span&gt;Heat a large chargrill pan on medium-high heat. Cook potato slices, in batches, for 2 to 3
            minutes or until charred. Transfer to a plate. Cook steak for 3 to 4 minutes each side, for medium, or until
            cooked to your liking. Transfer to a plate. Cover loosely with foil. Set aside for 5 minutes to rest.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 4&lt;/span&gt;Meanwhile, cook remaining curry paste in a small saucepan over medium-high heat for 2
            minutes. Add tamarind puree, sugar, sh sauce, peanut butter and coconut milk. Bring to a simmer. Reduce heat
            to medium. Simmer, stirring occasionally, for 4 to 5 minutes or until sauce thickens.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">1/4 cup massaman curry paste 2cm piece fresh ginger, finely grated 2 garlic cloves, crushed 1/2 lemongrass stalk, white part only, very finely chopped 600g beef rump steak, trimmed 2 tablespoons sweet chilli sauce 2 tablespoons white vinegar 3 baby cucumbers, thinly sliced into rounds 400g chat potatoes 1 tablespoon peanut oil 2 teaspoons tamarind puree 2 teaspoons brown sugar Method Step 1Combine 2 tablespoons curry paste with 1 tablespoon water, ginger, garlic and lemongrass. Place beef in a shallow glass or ceramic dish. Rub all over with paste mixture. Cover. Refrigerate for 3 hours or overnight. Step 2Place potatoes in a large saucepan. Cover with cold water. Bring to the boil over high heat. Reduce heat to medium. Boil for 10 to 12 minutes or until just tender. Drain. Cool for 15 minutes. Slice thickly. Drizzle with peanut oil. Season with salt and pepper. Step 3Heat a large chargrill pan on medium-high heat. Cook potato slices, in batches, for 2 to 3 minutes or until charred. Transfer to a plate. Cook steak for 3 to 4 minutes each side, for medium, or until cooked to your liking. Transfer to a plate. Cover loosely with foil. Set aside for 5 minutes to rest. Step 4Meanwhile, cook remaining curry paste in a small saucepan over medium-high heat for 2 minutes. Add tamarind puree, sugar, sh sauce, peanut butter and coconut milk. Bring to a simmer. Reduce heat to medium. Simmer, stirring occasionally, for 4 to 5 minutes or until sauce thickens.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rumen Burgers</title><link href="/2018/11/27/burgers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rumen Burgers" /><published>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/27/burgers</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/27/burgers.html">&lt;div class=&quot;ingredients-wrapper&quot;&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;4 x 100g pkts Nissin Ramen Noodle&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon soy sauce&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;300g beef mince&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;200g piece Kaiserfleisch (smoked pork), very finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons mirin seasoning&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;3 teaspoons white miso&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;85g (1/3 cup) Kewpie Mayonnaise&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons wasabi&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 green shallots, thinly sliced&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 teaspoon sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;80ml (1/3 cup) vegetable oil&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;4 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;method&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 class=&quot;header-method&quot;&gt;Method&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 1&lt;/span&gt;
            Grease eight 9.5cm (base measurement) round ramekins or ovenproof dishes with oil.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 2&lt;/span&gt;Discard noodle seasoning. Cook noodles in a saucepan of boiling water for 3 minutes or
            until tender. Drain. Divide among ramekins. Cover surface with plastic wrap. Place cans in dishes to press
            down. Place in fridge for 1 hour.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 3&lt;/span&gt;

            Meanwhile, for the pickled vegies, toss the ingredients in a bowl. Set aside for 1 hour.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 4&lt;/span&gt;
            Place soy in a bowl. Combine mince, pork, mirin and miso in a large bowl. Roll into 4 balls. Dip in soy.
            Flatten into patties. Place on a plate. Combine mayo and wasabi in a bowl. Combine shallot and sesame oil in
            a bowl.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 5&lt;/span&gt;

            Heat 3 tbs vegetable oil in a non-stick frying pan over medium heat. Use a flatbladed knife to loosen the
            noodles. Invert dish into pan to release buns. Cook, in batches, for 3-4 minutes each side or until golden.
            Drain on paper towel. Keep warm.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">4 x 100g pkts Nissin Ramen Noodle 1 tablespoon soy sauce 300g beef mince 200g piece Kaiserfleisch (smoked pork), very finely chopped 2 tablespoons mirin seasoning 3 teaspoons white miso 85g (1/3 cup) Kewpie Mayonnaise 2 teaspoons wasabi 2 green shallots, thinly sliced 1/2 teaspoon sesame oil 80ml (1/3 cup) vegetable oil 4 eggs Method Step 1 Grease eight 9.5cm (base measurement) round ramekins or ovenproof dishes with oil. Step 2Discard noodle seasoning. Cook noodles in a saucepan of boiling water for 3 minutes or until tender. Drain. Divide among ramekins. Cover surface with plastic wrap. Place cans in dishes to press down. Place in fridge for 1 hour. Step 3</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Colin’s doughnuts with lemon curd</title><link href="/2018/11/27/donuts.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Colin's doughnuts with lemon curd" /><published>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/27/donuts</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/27/donuts.html">&lt;div class=&quot;ingredients-wrapper&quot;&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;10g (about 1 1/2 pkts) dried yeast&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;125ml (1/2 cup) milk, warmed&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;275g plain flour&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;5g table salt&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;35g caster sugar&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 lemon, rind finely grated&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/4 vanilla bean, seeds scraped&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 egg&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 egg yolks&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;35g butter, at room temperature, chopped&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;100g caster sugar, extra&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;method&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 class=&quot;header-method&quot;&gt;Method&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 1&lt;/span&gt;
            For the doughnuts, combine the yeast and milk in a small bowl. Set aside for 5 minutes or until frothy.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 2&lt;/span&gt;Place flour, salt, sugar, rind and vanilla in the bowl of a stand mixer fitted with a
            dough hook. Mix until just combined. Whisk the egg and yolks in a bowl. With the motor running on low, add
            the yeast mixture to the flour mixture and mix until just combined. Add the egg mixture and mix until
            combined. Add the butter, beating for 5-10 minutes or until a smooth sticky dough forms. Transfer to a
            greased bowl. Cover. Set aside in a warm, draughtfree place for 45-60 minutes or until doubled in size.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 3&lt;/span&gt;
            Line a baking tray with baking paper. Use your fist to knock back dough. Divide dough into 40g portions.
            Roll each portion into a smooth ball. Place on prepared tray, leaving room for spreading. Cover with lightly
            greased plastic wrap and set aside to prove for 1 hour or until doubled in size.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 4&lt;/span&gt;
            Meanwhile, for the lemon curd, place the lemons in a large saucepan. Cover with water. Bring to the boil
            over high heat. Reduce heat to low. Simmer for 45-60 minutes or until very soft. Use a slotted spoon to
            transfer lemons to a bowl. Set aside to cool slightly. Reserve 50ml cooking liquid. Halve lemons. Discard
            seeds. Blend lemon and reserved liquid in a blender until smooth. Add the butter. Blend until combined.
            Transfer to a bowl. Stir in the sugar and salt. Place the curd in a piping bag fitted with a 1cm plain
            nozzle.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 5&lt;/span&gt;
            Combine cinnamon and extra sugar on a tray. Pour enough oil into a large saucepan to come halfway up the
            side. Heat over medium-low heat to 160C on a cook’s thermometer. Deep-fry doughnuts, in batches, turning,
            for 3-4 minutes or until puffed and golden. Transfer to sugar mixture and turn to coat.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">10g (about 1 1/2 pkts) dried yeast 125ml (1/2 cup) milk, warmed 275g plain flour 5g table salt 35g caster sugar 1/2 lemon, rind finely grated 1/4 vanilla bean, seeds scraped 1 egg 2 egg yolks 35g butter, at room temperature, chopped 1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon 100g caster sugar, extra Method Step 1 For the doughnuts, combine the yeast and milk in a small bowl. Set aside for 5 minutes or until frothy. Step 2Place flour, salt, sugar, rind and vanilla in the bowl of a stand mixer fitted with a dough hook. Mix until just combined. Whisk the egg and yolks in a bowl. With the motor running on low, add the yeast mixture to the flour mixture and mix until just combined. Add the egg mixture and mix until combined. Add the butter, beating for 5-10 minutes or until a smooth sticky dough forms. Transfer to a greased bowl. Cover. Set aside in a warm, draughtfree place for 45-60 minutes or until doubled in size. Step 3 Line a baking tray with baking paper. Use your fist to knock back dough. Divide dough into 40g portions. Roll each portion into a smooth ball. Place on prepared tray, leaving room for spreading. Cover with lightly greased plastic wrap and set aside to prove for 1 hour or until doubled in size. Step 4 Meanwhile, for the lemon curd, place the lemons in a large saucepan. Cover with water. Bring to the boil over high heat. Reduce heat to low. Simmer for 45-60 minutes or until very soft. Use a slotted spoon to transfer lemons to a bowl. Set aside to cool slightly. Reserve 50ml cooking liquid. Halve lemons. Discard seeds. Blend lemon and reserved liquid in a blender until smooth. Add the butter. Blend until combined. Transfer to a bowl. Stir in the sugar and salt. Place the curd in a piping bag fitted with a 1cm plain nozzle. Step 5 Combine cinnamon and extra sugar on a tray. Pour enough oil into a large saucepan to come halfway up the side. Heat over medium-low heat to 160C on a cook’s thermometer. Deep-fry doughnuts, in batches, turning, for 3-4 minutes or until puffed and golden. Transfer to sugar mixture and turn to coat.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ham and baked ricotta cheesecake platter</title><link href="/2018/11/27/baked-rikotta.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ham and baked ricotta cheesecake platter" /><published>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-27T18:13:20+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/27/baked-rikotta</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/27/baked-rikotta.html">&lt;div class=&quot;ingredients-wrapper&quot;&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;300g fresh ricotta&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 cup vintage cheddar, grated&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/3 cup parmesan, grated&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 egg yolks&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon fresh thyme leaves&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon fresh chives, finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 cup walnuts&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon icing sugar&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 bunch watercress, sprigs picked&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Leftover ham, chilled, sliced (see Notes)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 bunches asparagus, trimmed, steamed&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;250g Amoroso truss tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;method&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 class=&quot;header-method&quot;&gt;Method&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 1&lt;/span&gt;
            Preheat oven to 200C/180C. Grease two 4cm-deep, 11cm (base) round springform pans. Line base and sides with
            baking paper, extending paper 2cm above edges of pans.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 2&lt;/span&gt;Place ricotta, cheddar, parmesan, egg yolks, thyme and chives in a bowl. Season with salt
            and pepper. Stir until smooth and combined. Divide ricotta mixture evenly between prepared pans. Using a
            spatula, press ricotta mixture firmly into prepared pans, levelling tops. Place pans on a baking tray.
            Season with salt and pepper. Bake for 30 to 40 minutes or until golden and firm. Set aside to cool.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 3&lt;/span&gt;Meanwhile, heat a small non-stick frying pan over medium heat. Add walnuts. Stir for 2 to
            3 minutes or until toasted. Add sugar. Cook, stirring constantly, for 1 minute or until sugar melts and
            caramelises and walnuts are coated. Transfer to a baking paper-lined baking tray. Set aside to cool.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 4&lt;/span&gt;
            Make Honey Basil Dressing; Whisk honey, oil and vinegar in a small bowl. Stir in basil. Season with salt and
            pepper.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 5&lt;/span&gt;
            Carefully remove cheesecakes from pans. Arrange watercress, cheesecakes, sliced ham, asparagus and tomatoes
            on a serving board or platter. Scatter with walnuts and basil. Drizzle with dressing. Serve with crusty
            bread.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">300g fresh ricotta 1/2 cup vintage cheddar, grated 1/3 cup parmesan, grated 2 egg yolks 1 tablespoon fresh thyme leaves 1 tablespoon fresh chives, finely chopped 1/2 cup walnuts 1 tablespoon icing sugar 1 bunch watercress, sprigs picked Leftover ham, chilled, sliced (see Notes) 2 bunches asparagus, trimmed, steamed 250g Amoroso truss tomatoes Method Step 1 Preheat oven to 200C/180C. Grease two 4cm-deep, 11cm (base) round springform pans. Line base and sides with baking paper, extending paper 2cm above edges of pans. Step 2Place ricotta, cheddar, parmesan, egg yolks, thyme and chives in a bowl. Season with salt and pepper. Stir until smooth and combined. Divide ricotta mixture evenly between prepared pans. Using a spatula, press ricotta mixture firmly into prepared pans, levelling tops. Place pans on a baking tray. Season with salt and pepper. Bake for 30 to 40 minutes or until golden and firm. Set aside to cool. Step 3Meanwhile, heat a small non-stick frying pan over medium heat. Add walnuts. Stir for 2 to 3 minutes or until toasted. Add sugar. Cook, stirring constantly, for 1 minute or until sugar melts and caramelises and walnuts are coated. Transfer to a baking paper-lined baking tray. Set aside to cool. Step 4 Make Honey Basil Dressing; Whisk honey, oil and vinegar in a small bowl. Stir in basil. Season with salt and pepper. Step 5 Carefully remove cheesecakes from pans. Arrange watercress, cheesecakes, sliced ham, asparagus and tomatoes on a serving board or platter. Scatter with walnuts and basil. Drizzle with dressing. Serve with crusty bread.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tikka salmon with red lentil dahl</title><link href="/2018/11/23/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tikka salmon with red lentil dahl" /><published>2018-11-23T18:13:20+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-23T18:13:20+02:00</updated><id>/2018/11/23/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/23/first-post.html">&lt;div class=&quot;ingredients-wrapper&quot;&gt;
    &lt;ul class=&quot;ingredients&quot;&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/4 cup (70g) thick Greek-style yoghurt&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;3 tablespoons tikka curry paste&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;6 salmon cutlets&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 cup (200g) red lentils, rinsed, drained&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 teaspoon ground turmeric&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons sunflower oil&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1 red onion, thinly sliced&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 small dried chillies (see note)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 cup fresh curry leaves (see note)&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/2 teaspoon cumin seeds&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;1/4 teaspoon brown mustard seeds&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;2 garlic cloves, thinly sliced&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;method&quot;&gt;
        &lt;h2 class=&quot;header-method&quot;&gt;Method&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 1&lt;/span&gt;
            Combine yoghurt and curry paste in a bowl and season. Add salmon, turning to coat, then cover and chill
            until needed.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 2&lt;/span&gt;Place lentils, turmeric and 4 cups (1L) water in a pan. Bring to the boil, then reduce
            heat to low and simmer, stirring occasionally, for 8-10 minutes until lentils are soft but retain some
            texture. Set aside.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 3&lt;/span&gt;
            Place 1 tablespoon oil in a pan over medium heat. Cook onion for 2-3 minutes, stirring, until softened. Stir
            in chillies, curry leaves, spices, garlic and 1/2 teaspoon salt, then cook for 1 minute until fragrant. Stir
            into lentils.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 4&lt;/span&gt;
            Heat remaining 1 tablespoon oil in a pan. Cook fish for 2-3 minutes each side until almost cooked, but still rare in the centre.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step 5&lt;/span&gt;
            Divide dahl and salmon among plates. Serve with pappadams and chutney.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">1/4 cup (70g) thick Greek-style yoghurt 3 tablespoons tikka curry paste 6 salmon cutlets 1 cup (200g) red lentils, rinsed, drained 1/2 teaspoon ground turmeric 2 tablespoons sunflower oil 1 red onion, thinly sliced 2 small dried chillies (see note) 1/2 cup fresh curry leaves (see note) 1/2 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/4 teaspoon brown mustard seeds 2 garlic cloves, thinly sliced Method Step 1 Combine yoghurt and curry paste in a bowl and season. Add salmon, turning to coat, then cover and chill until needed. Step 2Place lentils, turmeric and 4 cups (1L) water in a pan. Bring to the boil, then reduce heat to low and simmer, stirring occasionally, for 8-10 minutes until lentils are soft but retain some texture. Set aside. Step 3 Place 1 tablespoon oil in a pan over medium heat. Cook onion for 2-3 minutes, stirring, until softened. Stir in chillies, curry leaves, spices, garlic and 1/2 teaspoon salt, then cook for 1 minute until fragrant. Stir into lentils. Step 4 Heat remaining 1 tablespoon oil in a pan. Cook fish for 2-3 minutes each side until almost cooked, but still rare in the centre. Step 5 Divide dahl and salmon among plates. Serve with pappadams and chutney.</summary></entry></feed>